MY BELOVED DEMON
Looks like your hell has just begun.
Tell me if you find the book.
Who knows?
Maybe she...
will open your way out of it.
He is to blame for everything!
No Suk Min killed both Mom and To Kyung!
And it was he who tried to kill To To Hee.
No Suk Min, that scoundrel,
and is the devil.
My mother didn't believe in anything
not to mention religion.
But she started almost every day
go to confession after their death!
Why do you think?
What was she so desperate to wash away?
What exactly was she so afraid of?
All signs of attention and love,
which she gave you
were actually her ticket to heaven.
This is a lie.
You lie!
Then ask her yourself.
Is she in hell or heaven
go and ask her yourself.
are you ok sir
Sir!
I finally get a chance to see your powers.
kill me
that we may go to hell together.
You will cease to exist if you kill a person.
Knowledge without power
can be dangerous.
Ku Vone!
Maybe I can't kill you
but torturing you is not a problem.
Eventually you'll be begging me to kill you.
Enough, Ku Won.
Let's hand him over to the police.
It makes no sense.
There will be no evidence.
They will not be able to touch
and hairs on my head.
There is one piece of evidence that you couldn't get rid of.
Kim...
Se La.
It's been a long time
my husband started to worry
that mom won't let him
to inherit her position.
That's why I prepared.
How did you gather all this information?
without his knowledge?
He respects…
that I don't know anything.
There is always a problem in the family.
I should have been kinder to my family.
Make a deal with me.
You can take my soul or whatever you want.
but please
make sure that about it
no one will know.
I will leave To Hee in the future.
I promise
As if I will believe it.
You are really evil.
Scoundrels like you
they are taking my job away.
Surrender, No Suk Mine.
You have nowhere to run.
You are wrong.
I can still run to hell.
No!
EPISODE 14
OUR PERSONAL HELL
All this for the sake of the position of chairman?
Is he the devil or something?
Can't believe that No Suk Min
fooled everyone all this time.
Have you contacted his family?
Yes, I contacted Ms. Noh Soo An
and Mr. Choo Seok Hoon.
If you think about it,
they are relatives of both the victim and the suspect.
God
Mrs. No.
Is this true?
Did my brother kill my mother?
I'm afraid so.
Chairman of "Mire Group" No Suk Min
committed suicide,
jumping off the building.
- Head of "Mire Group"?
- He was accused
in the high-profile assassination of Chairman Chu.
It turned out that he was standing
and on the recent embezzlement of funds
and official crimes
on an astronomical scale.
His body has not yet been found,
police…
Is he really dead?
If he were alive
i could find him.
I tried to find him
using force
but it didn't work out.
I should have arrived earlier.
sorry
Nothing.
It's empty.
Mr. Chong
Sorry for the no warning.
Are you on your way from the police station?
How is To Hee holding up?
Was the body found?
Not yet.
The search turned out to be difficult.
It seems that
for the body to float in the river, the moon will pass.
How is his wife?
Presumably, the police will immediately investigate the case,
because her shows are so detailed.
By the way, how did you convince her?
Forced her to realize reality.
People really are the scariest.
He killed his own mother
and framed his own son.
He used the whole family
as tools on the way.
People do more inhumane things,
than all other beings.
But Suk Min…
told me something strange.
What exactly?
What Ms. Chu
killed my parents
What? This is absurd.
Don't say you believe.
I know this is absurd.
But it confuses me.
Aunt Jung-suk had no reason to do that.
He said that his father visited her
on the day my parents died.
He blackmailed her
due to the prospect of a large investment.
Don't let yourself be embarrassed, To Hee.
I'm sure he made it up to even
in the last moments to hurt you.
What do you think
about No Suk Min's words?
This cannot be true.
It would not be better.
Aunt Jung Suk pulled To Hee out of hell.
If it turns out that she is
made To Hee go through hell
she will be simply devastated.
This would mean that the world
in which she believed
was just a lie.
Ku Vone.
What?
I'm just
I wanted to know that you are near.
I am near, I hug you.
Call me by my name.
I will answer every time.
Ku Vone.
Yes, To Hee.
Yes, I'm here.
CHAIRMAN OF "MIRE GROUP" NO SUK MIN
JUMPED OFF THE ROOF TO DEATH
They say the CEO is To To Hee
was at the scene
when No Suk Min's head jumped off the roof…
refer to the official statement.
- The article was inappropriate.
- This is a personal tragedy,
- but time will heal wounds.
- We don't plan
no interviews.
Our official statement…
- Hello? Do you hear?
- Hello?
are you listening Hello?
No time to waste energy on illogical demands
and get back to work.
To us
perform an exorcism or something?
Exorcism?
People die all the time.
There must be a reason.
I am convinced
our company is cursed or something.
Exorcism will be very expensive.
And I'm not sure
that it will happen at all.
Talk to Mrs. To?
- Regarding exorcism?
- Yes.
I ordered to return to work.
- Yes, ma'am.
Madam,
reporters everywhere.
Maybe become a wall
and help Mrs. To pass or something.
Good morning...
No, not a good morning.
How did she make her way through the crowd?
Do you want me to add jobs for you?
No need.
I organize the event.
We are very concerned, right?
Let's hurry up.
Come in.
You arrived safely.
Thanks to Ku Won's powers.
Chaos outside the door.
But let's be patient.
Soon everything will be forgotten.
Do I have to sign anything?
It's not for me.
This is for you.
Listen, you're trying
should I be so hot?
Everything is wrong.
We just had a black streak.
Don't worry. Everything is already behind.
You are more gullible than you seem.
It was expensive!
Here.
I appreciate your concern, Ms. Sin.
Of course.
You look remarkably like Mr. Pak.
I think I am close to her
a much more powerful talisman.
Come in.
Ms. Chin Ka Yeong has come to see you.
eat
This is the best food in the area.
Tomorrow is my last performance.
Is this an apology?
I don't believe in apologies.
As if a few words can fix everything.
People apologize to make it easier for them.
I did wrong
when she cheated on you
and longed for Mrs. To's death.
Just turn away.
To To Hee must die for you to live!
If you were in that situation again,
would you act differently?
No.
this is what i am
that's how much I love Principal Jeon.
I'll try to figure it out.
You once told me
that we have something in common.
So I will try to understand you.
Now eat.
- Notice here more carefully.
- Yes, sir.
"RICE SOUP ON SUNSHINE"
- Boss.
- Move.
We came out of the shadows
and found a legitimate job under the sun.
I…
Talkative!
Yes, sir!
What is it, sir?
Look at the sign.
Is it a seedling, not a shallot?
I'm sorry, sir.
I will take care of everything.
Please take care of it, chef.
Yes, sir.
Sorry!
That's not a shallot!
It's a mess.
To real men
need a large shallot!
I asked for shallots!
- Of course.
- What did I do wrong?
We will serve food with love.
Welcome to Rice Soup in the Sun.
I think it belongs to you.
"DEMON"
Goodbye then.
But Suk Min said
that Choo Jung Suk
killed To Hee's parents.
Is this news to you?
Yes.
But if he said that
I'm sure he's serious.
He believed that his mother was capable
even at worst.
"DEMON"
Director Chong!
But To Kyung was really not the intruder?
So how many attackers were there?
It looks like we have
a new intruder around every corner.
Is everything right this time?
- Mr. Pak.
- What?
Let's say...
you believe someone pulled you out of hell.
And then it turns out...
that this particular person sent you to hell.
What would you do?
I would burn bridges.
when they hurt you
best to burn bridges.
And if it's a dead person?
That's all decided. There is no problem.
But who is it about?
Choo Jung Suk.
Maybe she…
killed To Hee's parents.
Hold on.
That is, how could she possibly have killed them?
Did she kill them or not?
These are No Suk Min's words, so it remains to be seen.
What...
Did he tell you that before he died?
Probably, he is a real villain.
He was evil to the end.
So that's why you're so upset.
I think everything is confused.
It's too scary to unearth the truth
but she is too important
to simply ignore it.
But if I were her…
What?
I would deny it and move on.
In general, it is possible
to hide this?
It would hurt sometimes
like a rolling pin under the skin.
It's the same
i would choose imperfect happiness
and not the painful truth.
There should already be articles
about the sales rating of our new product.
BODY HEAD NO SUK MINA
NOT FOUND YET
My mother didn't believe in anything
not to mention religion.
But she started walking every day
to confession after their death!
Why do you think?
What was she so desperate to wash away?
What exactly was she so afraid of?
ACCIDENT AT PRODUCTION
"MIRE ELECTRONICS"
"ELECTRONIC MIRE" RECOGNIZED FOR THE FIRST TIME
ACCIDENT AT PRODUCTION
CHU CHONG SUK'S HEAD IS ON HIS KNEES
I will expose everything.
How dare you blackmail me?
What do you want?
Just wait.
Everything won't go the way you want it to.
All signs of attention and love,
which she gave you
were actually her ticket to heaven.
Yes, yes!
From the death of your parents
more than 20 years have passed.
You can no longer honor
the anniversary of their death.
Just celebrate your birthday.
How long have you worked for Ms. Chu?
I worked for her for about 20 years
to work with you.
you were with her
when she admitted to the accident
at the production of "Mire Electronics"
first time?
Yes.
I just started then
to work as her secretary.
When did she start using a wand?
She already used it
when we met
It was sometime when you met.
At your parents' funeral.
Something
then what happened
She never explained why.
We were only told that it is a chronic disease.
Ku Vone.
What should I do?
Ms. Chu did not approve of what I honored
the anniversary of the death of parents
on his birthday.
She kept insisting
so that I forget the unhappy past.
If what No Suk Min said is true
and Mrs. Chu really cheated me,
then what should i do?
seems to
like i'm trapped
Do you remember
the message that Choo Jung Suk
sent you before death?
She wrote that she loves you.
I LOVE YOU SO HEE
Even dying in agony
she wrote you
to express your love.
In the face of death
people are most honest with themselves.
This is what I observed
the past 200 years.
You are right.
It's a pity that the dead won't say anything anymore.
One conversation with her
I would decide everything.
Yes?
There is a way…
get the news he Ms. Chu.
How to get a message from Choo Jung-suk here?
She was close to the priest here
named Father Michael.
Maybe he is
can tell us something.
How should he know anything?
father
Of course.
Thanks to confession.
Long time no see, To Hee.
This is my husband.
I am Father Michael.
Jung Koo Won.
He speaks quite strangely.
Probably, he is not from local places.
by the way
how was Mrs. Chu's funeral?
I was a volunteer in Mongolia
and could not be present.
It was an eventful day.
I read about it in the newspapers.
Heard Suk Min died.
It is for this reason that I am here.
Before he died, he told me something strange.
Could you please
let us talk alone?
Can you wait outside the door?
Call me if anything happens.
Good.
I have a bad feeling about him.
Looks like the time has finally come.
Ms. Chu…
I felt guilty until the very end...
because she was not completely frank with you.
father
I won't be able to go to heaven, will I?
But there is something I fear more…
than go to hell.
I'm afraid…
that she will not forgive me.
Your own mind has locked you in hell.
Time to confess and tell the truth
to free yourself.
True...
If I can't find the courage
before death...
and…
if To Hee asks what the truth is
then I ask…
tell her you
Was that your order?
You ordered tampering
state measurement data
work environment?
It is only for a short time.
I will replace the dust collectors,
I have just finally received the investment.
"Just for a while"?
Meanwhile, people can die.
You say you are ready to trade
people's lives for investment?
Everything has its time.
Certain risks are acceptable
for higher purposes.
But you are not the one taking the risk!
By doing so, you are sacrificing employees,
who trusted you
for your personal success!
Our company is at a crossroads.
This is significant
investment offer - a rarity!
Do nothing.
Every goal
requires certain collateral losses.
You left me no choice.
I will expose everything.
How dare you blackmail me?
What do you want?
Money?
I only want you to take
take responsibility
and made sure that this would not happen again.
You left the company and ran away.
Who gave you that right?
This is my company.
You did not build it yourself.
It is built on blood, sweat and tears
everyone who works here!
Dear, it's okay.
We have almost no time left.
Just wait.
Everything will not go as you want.
My wife will send detailed documents
to your office.
The lives of hundreds of people are in danger.
This must be made public.
After what I've been through
to build a company
how dare you destroy her?
Beloved.
I have to take care of it
before i die
I will stop you even if it kills me.
By hand
Time, dear.
Don't worry.
I will have time to see To Hee before I die.
No!
TO HEE'S DEAR DAUGHTER
I'll come back
Beloved.
Please save my wife.
You can't make a wish.
You are ten years ago
already made a deal with me.
Please, I can't leave To Hee alone.
You will die of a heart attack.
To Hee
What is…
did you commit
Judging from your view,
I see you are desperate for something.
of what
Do you want me to fulfill your wish?
I can do it
your most cherished wish
and give you the life you want.
But you will repay me in ten years.
In ten years
your soul will end up in hell.
You probably…
the devil
Ms. Chu
she regretted that night all her life.
She always blamed herself
in what happened
thought that everything would be different
if she hadn't followed them.
What did he say?
But Suk Min lied.
Then why are you so upset?
I feel bad, even for a moment
doubted Mrs. Chu.
Come on.
I will wash and go to bed.
To Hee
Don't worry.
I'm just tired.
The event of that night
changed Mrs. Chu's attitude to life forever.
A meeting with a real devil...
didn't let her become a devil herself.
are you going somewhere
Yes, sign the agreement.
I usually work better at night.
go to sleep
Don't wait for me.
you are back
You probably understood who I am...
because it doesn't surprise you.
Why should I be surprised?
your existence
proves the existence of God.
Do you think God protects you?
Actually, I was waiting for you.
Leave To Hee.
You are dangerous for her.
You can't stay with her.
Perhaps the profession is to blame,
but you seem
You are biased towards me.
I do no harm.
At least To Hee.
you don't care
how do i know about you
Extraordinary aura and strange speech.
as soon as i saw you
i knew you were the devil
that Ms. Chu was talking about.
Are you saying Choo Jung-suk saw me?
She was present
when you were driving
To Hee's father to hell.
You can't make a wish.
You are ten years ago
already made a deal with me.
Please, I can't leave To Hee alone.
You probably…
the devil
Not recognizing a person after such a long time
quite expected.
as you know
people's time flies quickly and easily.
But just think
that the repetition of unfortunate fate,
which you so wanted to avoid
already happened
So you knew everything.
As I said,
you had to find out everything yourself.
People think I'm in control.
But...
I am only a companion on every path.
Ms. Chu.
I promised to be in a better mood,
but could not fulfill the promise.
If you were honest with me
would I fall in love with Ku Won?
What could my dad's wish have been?
I have to find out…
what deal did my father make?
who knows
did Koo Won save dad's life?
TERM OF VALIDITY OF THE AGREEMENT
Mrs. To.
Today is my last performance.
We couldn't get along
but I wanted to say goodbye.
Will you never go back to Korea?
No.
You have to be careful.
this is what happens
if a person falls in love with a demon.
I was joking.
I hope you will be happy
with or without Director Jeon.
Thank you.
I will be happy.
- Please take part in the event.
- Thank you.
Give us good feedback.
- Delicious.
The colors are so pretty.
- Can I taste it?
- Of course, please.
He is now very popular in social networks.
Will I become popular if I drink it?
Please give us good feedback.
- Have a nice day.
- Try our drinks.
Thank you.
I will carry
No, thank you.
Shall we bear it together?
I am so glad to see that you
- you get along, so...
- I'm alone.
She is herself.
Please give us good feedback.
Thank you.
Mr. Pak.
Congratulations.
Where is Director Jeon?
I went to sign the agreement.
He works so hard
since he got his strength back.
Can we talk alone?
Alone?
Mr. Pak, the director is looking for you.
go I will wait.
I'm not for long.
Will you wait in Director Chon's office?
- Of course.
- Okay.
- Quickly.
Urgent call of nature?
- Everything is more urgent with us, Mr. Paku.
- Good.
Let's do everything from the beginning!
I want to sign a new contract!
where is he
He should be here.
It's you, isn't it?
We signed an agreement ten years ago.
Finally we met again.
I was looking for you everywhere!
The agreement has been cancelled.
You can take it back
money, success, whatever.
Did you come all the way here to say that?
Back then, I was only interested in success.
I had the wrong priorities
and made a stupid choice.
From that day on, every day
regretted that choice.
I'm begging you.
I'll give everything I wanted
so please spare my life.
What do people think of as a demon?
Do I look like some kind of angel?
Please…
Look carefully.
That's what a demon is.
KIM CHI YEON
"Kim Chi-yong".
HONG SOK YEON
PAK MIN CHOL
That's all
names of those who signed agreements with him?
SING CHU YON
O KYU THE
PAK KYUNG MIN
My dad's name was also...
THAT'S WONG CHUN
When did you come here?
A man whose contract was expiring...
just broke into my office.
To the office?
To To Hee just went there.
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
To Hee
Did something happen?
i don't know what happened
but drink water and calm down.
What is it? what happened
Did something happen between you and Mr. Chong?
People I love…
became my hell.
I loved them with all my heart,
and now I hate it to death.
You were right.
In the end I…
I will equally bring grief to To Hee.
I'm just like that.
It's not just because you're a demon.
People
forever become each other's personal hell.
To Hee.
I have to find out
what deal my father made.
The event of that night...
A meeting with a real devil...
didn't let her become a devil herself.
Mrs. Chu felt guilty until the very end,
because she was not completely frank with you.
She was present,
when you drove
To Hee's father to hell.
If you were honest with me,
would I fall in love with Ku Won?
"MIRE NUTRITION"
Let's go for a walk.
are you cold
No.
To Hee
- We...
- Let's finish today
decorate the Christmas tree.
And I also have to book a couple of meals,
which we could not eat then.
I hope they are still available.
I don't think…
that we can spend Christmas together.
To Hee
Save yourself...
from hell
Ku Vone.
Ku Won has disappeared,
and my salvation has come to an end.
MY BELOVED DEMON
The more you loved me,
then suffered more.
But you loved me all the same.
We would have ended up the same way.
I'm leaving for a while.
Until To Hee finds
your happy ending without me.
Everything is back to normal and everything.
So you think it can harm me?
No way. Everything is fine.
A week has passed,
and the body of Chairman No Suk Min has not been found yet.
Is it possible…
Not yet found
no evidence about the head.
Translation of subtitles: Daria Hochel